(Between Fantasy and Reality)
Nice to see you, everyone.
You two haven't met yet, right?
- We haven't. It's nice to meet you. - It's nice to meet you. Hello.
- My gosh. - Hello.
Have you watched some of his clips?
- They were quite bold. - Right.
And he gives off this vibe...
- of a man living in nature. - Yes.
That's putting it nicely.
You know, she's a sweet girl.
But he doesn't give off that vibe...
- in the studio. - Yes.
- Does he look normal enough? - Right.
(A normal smile)
"He looks normal."
- Is that what you mean? - He looks normal and all.
That's a lengthy way of saying he looks surprisingly normal.
(That's a lengthy way of saying he looks surprisingly normal.)
(Beware of Fantasy)
(Chirping)
(As the chirping sound of the birds becomes his lullaby,)
(Dae Ho is enjoying his restful day.)
Yes. This is what I'm dreaming of.
That's such a happy moment.
Lying down there in my work pants. Yes, that's it.
This makes living in Seoul feel different.
- You can hear the birds... - Right.
- and the bugs... - Yes.
when you live in a single-family house.
I'm so envious of this.
(Getting up)
(Dae Ho walks out on top of the rooftop.)
What a mess.
(What a mess.)
What is that?
(The greenery is thick enough to cover the sky.)
(It's surrounded by overgrown grass.)
(Dae Ho's house has become a jungle.)
That's me.
(Even the wild animals can live safely in a place like this.)
(Munching)
CODE KUNST, you can go there and climb a tree.
That was tasty.
My gosh.
I've been busy this year.
On top of that, it rained a lot.
- I haven't seen this much rain. - Me neither.
When the rainy season was nearing,
I took a look at my house.
The house I used to remember is gone now.
(Dae Ho's cozy fun space...)
The grass was overgrown everywhere like a tropical rain forest.
Even I was surprised.
What? How many days has it been since you last took care of it?
It's only been two weeks.
It's the mountain.
- It's near a mountain. - That's why it grows faster.
- That happened in two weeks? - Yes.
You need to pull it out, though.
If I don't, it could damage the house.
- Right. It could damage the house. - I...
- But you... - Can it cover up the house?
- Right. That's because... - Yes.
- Roots could damage the house. - Yes.
- The roots penetrate into the gaps. - They can pierce through the walls.
- They can separate concrete walls. - My gosh.
Plants can be really strong.
(Fascinated)
This is a mess.
You have two houses, but you're usually on the rooftop.
(He comes down from the rooftop and enters House 1.)
Nana.
Nana, my legs are killing me. Gosh.
(What am I going to do with the tropical rain forest?)
- My legs are killing me. - So cute.
- Nana. - It's been a while, Nana.
So he's practically a wild cat.
He's living the life of a cheetah...
- in the Serengeti. - Like a wild animal.
(I like the wilderness that is my home.)
Nana, I'll be back.
(He says bye to Nana who's living in the wild.)
(He goes out with a backpack on.)
You're going out in those pants.
- At least he's wearing pants. - Right.
That's right.
I actually thought, "He bought new pants."
- I had the same thought. - Right.
- That's right. - The floral pants are new.
- "I haven't seen those pants." - I haven't seen them before.
That crossed my mind.
(Dae Ho is finally out of his winter clothes.)
- I spent a fortune on them. - My gosh.
A fortune?
(Dae Ho is wearing an expensive outfit outside.)
(Sighing)
(He stops walking only after taking a few steps.)
What is it?
- What happened? - What?
- Did Damarghini run into the house? - What a mess.
No. It didn't.
- My gosh. - What happened?
- Seriously. It looks doomed. - Wait. This is...
- Right. - Yes, this is like "I Am Legend."
- Gosh. - Or "Mars on Earth."
It's that fertile?
(Horrified)
(Daunting)
- It's that tree. That especially... - That tree is the worst.
- That's the problem. Yes. - That's the problem.
- That's the crazy one. - Seriously.
- You must pull it when you see it. - Right.
That's scary.
- Its life force is amazing. - It's crazy.
Gosh, that's a mess too.
I'm sorry. My gosh.
It rained way too much this year.
Vivarium enthusiasts say, "It's grown rampant."
There's a time...
- it hits a crazy growth period. - Right.
- It's like an explosion. - It happens out of the blue.
The vines that swallowed my car...
weren't there before.
It only took two weeks.
Within two weeks, they covered up the window shield of my car.
Where can you even start?
- Gosh. - I'd be so lost.
- Seriously. - I'm worried the car broke down.
(I don't know what to do, but I must save Damarghini.)
I needed to use scissors to remove them.
- Even a sickle is useless here. - I see.
- You must pull them by hand. - They're so tough.
- Really? - Yes.
- Pull them by hand. - They all cling onto each other.
- They're like never-ending vines. - Yes.
(He starts playing a tug of war with the vines.)
Gosh, what happened here?
Why is that coming out of my truck?
- It got inside. - This...
- Gosh, that's crazy. - Goodness.
I can't even tell how much of my car is covered in vines.
Why did this grow inside my car?
- I bet it's everywhere. - My gosh.
(Getting the creeps)
How did it get inside here? Wait.
Oh, no.
The thing is that, it went inside the wheel.
Even if I tried to pull it out,
I couldn't tell how deep the root was.
- That's crazy. - It kept coming out.
I still don't know. I removed everything visible to my eye,
but there could still be more vines, wrapping around parts of my car.
I was shocked.
Gosh, it got all the way inside my car.
- But aren't they really prickly? - They're so prickly.
Right. I remember them being very prickly.
Gosh, that's prickly.
Darn.
(He overcomes the prickly bushes and keeps working at it.)
(Losing his balance)
- Gosh. - They coiled around my house.
(The battle against the vines doesn't seem to end.)
(Sticking on his shirt)
I thought the leaves were a part of the original design.
(With the unexpected presents on his T-shirt,)
(he successfully rescues Damarghini.)
Okay.
(He gets into Damarghini right after the clean-up.)
(His heart is pounding for some reason.)
Let's go, Dama.
- It's still operating. - It's still working really well.
(He sets out to soothe Damarghini for what it has to put up with.)
Let's go.
- I got a vehicle inspection. - Yes.
- It's in perfect condition. - It's operating well.
- I was told to give it more oil. - Yes.
Gosh, this is the place.
(He arrives at his destination.)
Okay.
- You left in those stretchy pants. - This is the place. Okay.
He went to the downtown area in those stretchy pants.
(Impressed)
(He arrives at a self-service car wash in his unusual outfit.)
He went to wash his car.
I've done that about 100 times.
Really?
That's fun.
Right now, Damarghini...
has been with me for five years. It's been that long.
I've been busy. So unlike before,
I felt that I haven't done much to take care of it.
(Damarghini, we used to be so happy together.)
It's been out in the rain and snow so many times.
The exterior of my car seemed very dusty.
So Damarghini must be itchy all over.
I wanted to give it a bath.
- That's why I went there. - I've never seen anyone...
so attached to their car...
since the cartoon, "Bumpety Boo."
To tell you the truth, I had never washed...
Damarghini before. Not even once.
Really?
Once it rained,
- that counted as a car wash. - Sure.
You saved five years' worth...
- of car wash fees. - Right.
It's been out in the rain so much.
So the seats were covered in mold.
(A thick layer of old dust and dirt)
- Gosh, you never cleaned it. - It was still there.
(Mold has taken over the car.)
- Gosh. - Oh, no.
I never want to ride his truck again.
It was a terrifying memory.
(Trembling in fear)
I thought about getting the automatic car wash.
But I have a rack on the roof of my truck.
Because of the height, automatic car washes weren't...
- Right. You must remove that first. - an option.
What a great excuse.
I had never been there before.
I didn't know where to start or how to go about this.
I was excited and nervous at the same time.
That's how I felt. I was scared too.
How do I do this?
I was new to it. So I was completely lost.
(The newbie is lost from the beginning.)
(Dazed)
(Clicking)
You should put in the money first.
- I see. I must put in money. - I thought I could just start.
I thought I had to pay at the end.
Right. Nothing is free in life.
(He tries to pay for it with his phone.)
(Quiet)
What? Why isn't it working?
Did you try to pay with your transportation card?
- No. With my phone. - Is that the T-money card?
(Tapping)
(No matter how many times he puts it there, it doesn't work.)
You'll have to insert their card.
I don't think they accept credit cards.
There are special cards just for the car washes.
(Pressing on it)
Hold on. Why...
(Is this out of order?)
Why isn't it working?
- That's... - You just have to read the signs.
You just have to read the signs.
Right.
(It's all over the car wash.)
There it is.
- It said to get a card there. - That's the instruction.
Come on, man. You have to buy the card first.
The card for the car washes.
It says, "Please."
When I was there, I was completely clueless.
Those words failed me.
- I was flustered. - Really?
- But I know how that feels. - Right.
When I went to a self-service gas station for the first time,
there was an overwhelming vibe.
- I didn't want to mess it up. - She has everyone's back.
- She does. - That's right.
- She's so kind. - That's what I wanted to say.
- That's... - Didn't you feel overwhelmed?
- I did. - In case you pressed the wrong one.
Wait. I can't pay it with my phone?
Is he in there?
Excuse me.
- Hello. - Yes.
You can top up the card with the amount you want.
- You can tap the card on it. - I see.
That's 21 dollars.
- Okay. - The card costs a dollar.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- It worked. - It worked.
(He manages to pay at last.)
(The timer begins as soon as the payment goes through.)
The time limit makes you nervous.
(Staring)
What? Did it start?
I'm not ready yet.
(Rummaging through)
(He brought rubber gloves from his home.)
(He gets fully ready for his first car wash.)
Gosh, he already wasted the first cycle.
(Slow)
Darn.
My gosh.
I didn't know it'd start right away.
- But... - You thought you had to use water.
- Exactly. - I see.
- Oh, no. - But the timer started right away.
(He's taking his sweet time without looking at the timer.)
Why isn't it working?
Press it now.
Do I press this?
My gosh.
(He finally begins and has wasted 1 minute and 10 seconds.)
- Gosh, that's scary. - My gosh.
- The water came out right away. - My gosh.
(Surprised)
The water came out strong.
That feels great.
- Gosh, this looks like a game. - This hits the spot.
(This hits the spot.)
- The water pressure is good there. - That must feel good.
- It felt great. - It felt so good.
That must hit the spot.
(It's time to wash off the dirt and make it look spotless.)
I should've come here a long time ago. This is so convenient.
Gosh, this is amazing.
My gosh, that hits the spot.
(Thoroughly enjoying)
(Stopping)
What?
- Oh, no. - What?
Your time is up.
- You took your sweet time. - What?
I have to pay again?
- Gosh. Oh, no. - My goodness.
I must hurry up.
Gosh, that hits the spot.
(Washing every nook and cranny of his car thoroughly)
Why did you do that? There's a system that cleans the bottom.
- They didn't have it there. - It's not working.
Four, three, two...
- Yes, they have it. - They got it. There it is.
- The sign... - It says so on the board.
Learn how to read Korean, not how to wash cars.
When did your brain start betraying you?
It must've stopped working when he cried that day.
When Kian84 cried? That was...
Darn it.
(Tears, the friendship formula of men born in 1984)
Four, three, two...
- What? - Gosh.
- I know. I like that. - Wait.
I only had two seconds left.
- It was a waste. - You should use them up.
- Like the last minute at karaoke. - Right.
It's like the song, "100 Great People Who Made Korea Shine."
Is this it?
That's it.
(He sprays the detergent foam.)
That step feels good.
- Gosh, this is fun. - That was fun.
That ought to feel good.
(White snow falls on top of Damarghini.)
This is fun.
(Chuckling)
What? Darn.
(He's not even halfway through with the detergent.)
The cycles were too short.
(He pays again.)
This feels cool.
What?
Gosh, he couldn't finish spraying in the back.
This is...
What? Again?
Will you spend 300 dollars there?
- Did you spend all of it? - "Insufficient fund?"
(In no time, he blows through 20 dollars.)
You already spent 20 dollars there?
- Just get a regular car wash. - No way.
A regular car wash might be better.
Given that this is his 1st time, 20 dollars is a modest amount.
- Really? - Most newbies usually spend...
- a lot more money than... - Right.
they would for regular car washes.
I've watched other people who were good at this.
I've seen Gaeko do it.
He just sprayed it a few times.
He could do it within two minutes and still have time left.
That's enough time.
You kept spraying at the same spots.
- Right. - You need to learn some tips.
He didn't know.
- Sir. - Yes.
- Could you top up 20 more dollars? - You need more money, right?
- I ran out. - Right.
I was watching you. It looked like it was inevitable.
Top up 20 dollars, please.
- Twenty dollars? - Yes.
(Total expense: 40 dollars)
- Forty dollars? - Thank you.
- That's the fee for a regular one. - Okay.
I must start over.
- You're doing it again? - You're spraying detergent again?
- You can stop doing that. - That's enough!
- That's... - It should be all white.
Are you trying to bleach your car?
I sprayed a lot of detergent because I can't trust myself.
It felt like it would be clean if my truck completely turned white.
I can understand that. I feel the same way.
- Let's see how long you can do it. - Do you mean that?
- Do you mean that, Joy? - That's...
Yes. Seeing it covered in foam will put you at ease, right?
- Right. - I'd feel the same way.
(Mother Joresa is quite understanding.)
Okay. Gosh, I didn't know the trick.
- Okay. - It looks beautiful.
It does.
- It's like you painted it white. - Yes.
It must look as white as that to reassure me.
(He grabs something.)
This isn't easy.
(He removes the caked dirt himself.)
Isn't that a loofah sponge?
Can he use a loofah sponge?
People use soft sponges on cars.
I didn't know. I thought...
- Soft ones. - I could use any sponge.
Why didn't you use a stainless steel sponge then?
- I'm not that dense. - Gosh.
Doesn't it feel great?
(I'm sorry for neglecting you all these years.)
That must feel clean.
(Let's meet again, fresh and renewed.)
Doesn't it feel great?
Gosh, it's dripping with dirty water.
What?
Oh, my. Look at this, dripping with dirty water.
- Look. The water is black. - Gosh.
It's that dirty?
Gosh, it's dripping with dirty water.
What?
Oh, my. Look at this, dripping with dirty water.
- Look. The water is black. - Gosh.
It's that dirty?
(The Rainbow Club members are speechless.)
Joy, don't you have something to tell me?
- Joy is slowly giving up. - Yes.
This is your first time.
- This is understandable. - Yes.
(Anticipating)
She's saying it half-heartedly now.
Why is it so black?
- The water could turn black... - What's this?
- if you had never washed your car. - Yes.
(He doesn't stop scrubbing his car.)
(Dripping with dirty water)
- Your truck is crying. - My gosh.
- You must feel so bad... - Joy...
- Right. I really felt bad. - for your truck.
Gosh, I was shocked. Seriously.
I really thought Damarghini...
was possessed by an evil spirit.
Seriously. How could water turn that black?
Seriously. The black water...
I was like, "What's this?"
I thought water would turn that dark after smokey eye makeup.
I'm inside!
It looks like your truck is really crying.
Right. The more I scrubbed it, the more dirty water came out.
- You must perform an exorcism. - Right.
The dirty water kept coming out.
I had to scrub it.
So I kept scrubbing. It didn't seem to end.
This could be a chance to reflect on your behavior too.
Of course.
- Slowly, she's... - She's telling you to reflect.
- That was the point. Right? - Yes.
It might be better to say...
- an evil spirit possessed his car. - Yes.
(Let me see.)
(Wiping)
(He tries to gather the black tears with care.)
- Why did you save that? - Why did you do that?
- What are you doing? - Why?
I needed more detergent...
- for the top of my truck. - I see. For the top.
I thought you would take that home and use it while you took a shower.
- Me too. I really thought... - He's gathering that,
- so he can wash dishes at home. - My gosh.
You're a planner.
- Yes. - He's got a plan and tricks.
(He gathers every precious drop of it.)
- Look. That's a lot. - Gosh.
- It'd be a waste not to use it. - Gosh.
(He sprinkles the black tears to the top of his truck.)
I must do it right when I do it. This is exhausting.
Let's clean it thoroughly.
(With the collected black tears...)
I'm done scrubbing off the dirt.
(he finishes scrubbing the truck with detergent.)
Gosh, I must pay again.
- Sir. - You ran out, right?
Yes. Top up 20 more dollars, please.
It must be because this is your first time.
Usually, it doesn't cost this much.
- Is that so? - Yes.
How much does it usually cost?
It usually costs 10 to 12 dollars.
- Right. - Really?
- Usually, yes. - Dads usually finish it...
around ten dollars.
I thought about it, but it's impossible to finish it...
- only with ten dollars. - You need to know...
exactly where to go and how to spray it.
How can any finish this with ten dollars?
Wash?
What's that? Look at that.
Look! He damaged the paint.
See? It's got marks now.
What? What happened here?
You'll have to wash it again.
But it looks dirtier.
I think Damarghini is possessed by an evil spirit.
(Teary-eyed)
Why does it look dirtier?
(What happened to my truck?)
(Deducting 4 dollars)
He's using detergent again. Oh, no!
Again?
At this rate, it'll cost as much as his truck.
(He washes his truck...)
(nonstop.)
(But the black tear stains won't come off.)
- It's coming from the rubber. - Yes.
(Sighing)
Why do I feel bad?
(Insufficient fund)
He ran out?
How much money did I spend?
I'm blowing up my money here.
(Sweating profusely)
Why does my truck keep dripping with black water?
I noticed that it was coming...
- from the rubber strips. - Yes.
- The rubber strips are old. - I see.
- When you scrub them, - It's from the rubber strips.
- Yes. - Yes.
Here you go.
- Thank you. - Seventy dollars?
- Okay. - It costs more than regular ones.
(Stopping)
Can I have some water?
- Sure. - I was so thirsty.
- Thank you. - Pay ten dollars.
You should've tapped the card for drinking water.
- Seriously. - "That's 20 dollars."
I bet you dropped 3kg the next day.
It was because of the rubber strips.
My gosh.
Oh, that.
I can use the foam brush.
I wonder why he didn't think to use that up until now.
- Right. - The foam brush.
The foam brush.
- I like that. - That's nice.
- That's a great tool. - My gosh.
My gosh.
Yes, this is it.
- It's working now. - It got so easy with that.
- Yes. - That looks convenient.
With that, you didn't have to collect the foam for the top.
- Yes. - Right.
(Deducting 4 dollars)
(He's using the water hose at the same time.)
I can do this.
- I started to get the hang of it. - If you left it for a long time,
it might leave a stain?
- I got it. - Yes, that's why.
The dirt didn't come out if I didn't scrub it.
It came out only when I scrubbed it.
(Giggling)
It's working.
(Damarghini is gradually turning white.)
It felt great to watch my truck...
getting cleaned.
Gosh, this is exhausting.
Did it improve?
It's gotten cleaner.
By the way, it looks really clean.
(Damarghini is crying less now.)
- It looks clean now. - He's finally pulling out his car.
(He has to wipe the moisture outside the booth.)
Gosh, washing a car isn't an easy task.
I must take everything.
I had to clean up after myself.
(He picks up all of his trash and takes it with him.)
- I see. The foam? - What?
(He's spraying water on the ground?)
Did you spend money to clean up?
Do you have to wash the ground afterward?
- You don't have to do that. - People don't do that.
The thing is,
a truly beautiful person makes...
- wherever they stay look beautiful. - Right.
The dirty water from Damarghini...
was darker than I thought.
I rinsed the booth as a matter of etiquette.
- So... - Dae Ho, clean your house...
with that attitude.
(Dae Ho, clean your house with that attitude.)
But we ought to learn that from you.
You should wash the owner's back too.
That's right.
That's right. You should do that.
(He washes the top of the car thoroughly.)
(He wipes off the remaining water.)
(Groaning)
This is nice.
(Is this the end?)
Gosh.
I'm done.
Why don't you clean the interior of the van?
Cleaning the interior...
It'll take him 1 night and 2 days to clean the interior of the van.
All done.
(Let's leave behind the past of getting covered in plants.)
I washed the van for hours.
(Damarghini got a wash for the 1st time in 5 years.)
It's clean.
What?
That always happens.
What's that?
Why didn't you remove that?
What's up with the leaf?
He left it like a bookmark.
- It's like a hair streak. - "I read it up to here."
It's romance.
I feel refreshed.
(It's refreshing and nice.)
(Total time: 1 hour and 35 minutes, Total cost: 68 dollars)
It looks clean.
My goodness.
You wasted your time.
- This is driving me crazy. - You wasted your time.
It gives you a strange sense of accomplishment.
Just think that you paid for a sense of accomplishment.
I got to relieve my feeling of guilt regarding Damarghini.
That's right. You paid for a sense of accomplishment.
I feel refreshed.
(Feeling refreshed, he hits the road.)
I'm home.
(Sweet home)
It's clean.
(The car wash outing was pretty refreshing.)
All right.
(He goes to House 2 as he hums a tune.)
(Turning on the light)
The bathtub is nice.
- I love that room. - That room is so nice.
- His house is so clean. - It's nice.
(The comic book room that's full of dreams...)
I feel a sense of accomplishment.
(got more comic books.)
- You're maintaining it well. - I'm using it well.
(The innovative liquor room)
I see many more liquors.
What happened to the movie room?
- That isn't half bad. - Sometimes, I sleep there.
(Wearing slippers, he enters...)
(the vivarium room.)
You haven't killed them off.
I see more vivariums.
I'm doing my absolute best to fill the tanks.
(His vivariums were either dead...)
(or empty.)
They're growing nicely.
He's a true expert.
He has set them up so nicely.
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
It's a salamander.
(Cute friends have been added.)
There are a lot.
(He puts down the pieces of wood he found in the vivarium room.)
- There are many such items. - What are those?
Will you turn your house into a vivarium?
No.
(No way)
I need to create borders.
(He pulls out a chunk of clay.)
What's that?
- His house will become a vivarium! - I guess so.
- He wants to be a salamander. - Will you become a salamander?
He wants to be a salamander.
Maybe he'll stick to the wall.
All done.
(As the panelists speculate, he finishes the wooden border.)
(Opening)
- What's that? - What's that?
Is it moss?
It's impossible to predict what's inside.
(Gosh!)
(He works his muscles to bring over a mysterious box.)
(The boxes pile up.)
Oh, my!
(The light suddenly goes out.)
What's going on?
(What?)
It's a short circuit.
I set up electricity again,
but there was a leak when it rained a lot.
Whenever I turned on the air conditioner,
the circuit breaker tripped after 10 to 15 minutes.
Now that I've lived here for a while,
I think living in a house is harder in summer than in winter.
You have two options.
You can either maintain the house meticulously and diligently...
like Na Rae or KEY...
or leave the house alone like me.
You need to fall into 1 of those 2 categories.
If you're an in-betweener, living in a house will be hard.
It's definitely like that.
Given President Jun's tendencies,
he'll struggle if he lives in a house.
I know what he can do.
Why doesn't he have a trial period by living in a small house?
No place beats my house.
If President Jun is...
open to a short-term rental,
I want to try living in an apartment.
President Jun and I could switch places for a day.
I can't imagine Dae Ho in that apartment.
- I know. - I want to see him in that setting.
What have I done to deserve that?
- Nothing. - You wanted to live in a house!
Why do I need to live in an abandoned house?
- I mean... - Why do I need to do that?
Dae Ho lives there!
Why do I need to live in an abandoned house?
- Dae Ho lives there! - Don't call it an abandoned house.
He lives there.
- An abandoned house! - It looks more abandoned...
- than an abandoned house. - Don't call it that.
Dae Ho lives there.
It's an occupied house.
On the deck outside,
I'll leave out some tasks for him.
It'll be nice if he does them.
It's a good idea.
It's an exclusive offer for President Jun.
Right.
For goodness' sake.
The hotter, the better.
How could you tell me to live there when the electricity is out?
(I'll fight heat with heat!)
(He moves the heavy boxes without resting.)
The last one.
He's doing that without air conditioning.
(The place is full of boxes.)
(He finally reveals what's inside the box.)
(Heave-ho)
- It's rice. - Clay?
- Rice! - What?
- It looks like clay. - What is he doing?
What on earth is he doing?
(Mysterious substance in white is piled up.)
(Shall I open it now?)
(Sand pours out.)
What?
What a lunatic!
(Dae Ho, come on.)
This is actually insane.
(Sand pours out to the floor.)
No way.
(Grinning)
(Giggling)
He's crazy about entertainment.
(It looked like he had chased away the evil spirit of Damarghini.)
(Cutting)
(Laughing like a maniac)
- What on earth are you doing? - Seriously.
(Did the evil spirit possess Dae Ho this time?)
I can't believe it.
It really must be bad spirit.
(How scary)
In my house, I'll make the feature that has been a long-cherished wish.
I'll make a beach.
- I see. - I see.
(A beach?)
- You know, you should do it once. - That's right.
Had I been a child, I would've loved to have...
an uncle like him.
Joy, do you want to try living in a house?
Not at all.
The first beach I've visited abroad was in Cebu.
When I saw the white sandy beach,
I thought, "It'll be nice to keep this by my side..."
"and enjoy it at all times."
I've always had that thought.
As I built the second house,
I realized that it was possible.
(Movie room,)
(liquor room,)
(comic book room, etc)
(He designed House 2 with his dreams.)
(Adding a sandy beach of his dream will be the grand finale.)
That was the reason why I put tiles on the patio.
In the initial stage of construction,
there was a talk of putting a heating system underneath.
However, I opted for laying the groundwork for my dream.
If you install a heating system, you'll get a hot sand bath.
That's right. She's smart.
"How will I get rid of the sand later?"
"How will I maintain it?"
With that mindset, I won't be able to do anything.
- I just need to do it, - He's right.
I'm like that. When I do something I want,
I don't worry about the things that haven't happened.
"It'll be a hassle if I do this. Let's just not do it."
Then you'll die without doing it once in your life.
- I think it's nice. - He's totally insane.
Imagine thinking on your deathbed,
"I should've recreated a beach of Cebu."
It'll be useless.
It's better to die after doing what you wanted.
This place is like Cebu.
(He puts aside the worries regarding sand.)
It's the sea.
Let's go this way.
(A glint of happiness)
Look at that madness.
This is incredible.
(The beach is nearly done.)
It really feels like the sea.
The sand is so fine.
A beach in Cebu was like this.
You should add some palm trees and cacti.
He should dig into the sand...
- and sleep like a lizard. - That's right.
He should lay eggs there in winter.
- What? - Is he a sea turtle?
Like a sea turtle?
(Laughing)
To this...
(Hold on a second.)
Oh, my.
(A rattan parasol you see on beaches appears.)
He has finally gone insane.
(He's just happy about making his dream come true.)
I got it from the friend...
whose restaurant went out of business.
I'll put it here.
(This is it!)
(I'll make my dream come true.)
All right.
How about a sunlounger?
- I don't have a sunlounger. - Is that so?
I'll give you one. I have a sunlounger.
(Let's see.)
You should get more sand and make the beach more substantial.
- There should be... - The sand should cover you.
- hills like sand dunes. - That's right. "Dune."
- "Dune." How about "Dune?" - "Dune."
That sounds nice.
There should be enough sand for you to dig into.
- I'll be able to enjoy sledding. - That's right.
- That's right. - If you install a big fan,
- you'll create a sandstorm. - See? Everyone became imaginative.
- You'll be able to sand surf. - That sounds lovely.
(After laying out the sand, he suddenly rips up a box.)
(Then he takes a pen and sits on the sand.)
(He writes something diligently.)
(Giggling)
Daeundae.
(The 1-dimensional naming makes him laugh.)
Undae.
He wrote, "Daeundea."
(Laughing)
- What's "Daeundea?" - Is it incorrect?
It should be "Dae."
I didn't know.
It's misspelled!
You should know how to write Korean names in English.
You're an announcer.
You wrote "Dae" correctly.
He got the first part right.
"Daeundea." It sounds like he got a burn.
(Laughing)
(Not knowing about the mistake, he's satisfied.)
Daeundae is open.
(The next Haeundae,)
(Daeundea)
(It's a private vacation spot he made by scattering sand.)
It really feels like Cebu.
It's so pretty. I'm so satisfied.
Okay.
Daeundae is open.
- Daeundea. - Daeundea.
Daeundea!
Hey!
(What is going on so suddenly?)
This is your chance to leave.
(I'm warning you.)
(He suddenly takes off his top.)
(Sand falls.)
Your body looks pretty nice.
His body has improved.
- He has chest muscles. - What happened?
- I began working out. - What happened?
I began working out.
You lost some body fat.
- His chest is broad. - Yes.
(This cool body needs to lie down.)
I'm bulking up these days.
This is incredible.
(He lies down and enjoys the sand of Daeundea.)
(Wriggling)
What? He's laying eggs.
He's laying eggs.
It's a sea turtle's nesting season.
A sea turtle is preparing to lay eggs.
(Dae Ho Turtle digs up the sand of Daeundea.)
(A real sea turtle digs up sand in the same fashion.)
- It's the nesting season. - How bizarre.
You keep talking about such things, so I feel strange.
- That's how sea turtles lay eggs. - That's right.
(Breathing hard)
(He suddenly becomes absorbed in exercising.)
- Did you eat something bad? - No.
Six.
(He becomes sweaty in no time.)
Seven.
Gangneung has Muscle Beach.
(CODE KUNST and Sung Bin visited the place together.)
(It's a gym at the beach of Gangneung.)
If I exercise like I'm at a beach, I'll sweat more.
Right afterward, I'll be able to have a bath.
Thus, I decided to make the Muscle Beach.
These days, Kian84 is very fit.
(Gosh!)
What?
It's nothing.
"He's a friend of mine who's in his 40s just like me."
"Shouldn't I exercise like him?"
I had that thought.
- Thus, I began exercising at home. - He has lost a lot of weight.
I hike Mount Inwang often.
Stop pretending to be sexy!
(Here comes the sexy and hot guy of Daeundea!)
(Squats)
I'm good at squats.
You'll do 100.
I don't think I can do it.
- I can do it. - He exercises.
It's the Muscle Beach.
- Right away. - I can do it.
(A break is a luxury. Let's start doing push-ups.)
His belly is big.
- It's a fetal movement. - A fetal movement.
(Dae Ho Turtle's intense exercise leads to a fetal movement.)
- It's a fetal movement. - The baby is kicking.
- It's a boy. - The baby is kicking.
- "It's a boy." - It's an egg.
- Why would an egg kick? - It's an egg.
Its legs came out of the egg first.
Gosh, his belly looks ugly.
(My friend)
It's because he's pregnant.
He's carrying an egg.
They're teasing me because we're close.
I didn't want her to misunderstand.
I can do it.
- One. Two. - What's up with your belly?
Hey, your belly...
Gosh, his body is so ugly.
You know, you can't have...
a fit body from the start. I need to improve my body now.
- I think it has turned worse. - I need to improve it.
I'm exhausted.
He's exercising alone at home, so it's okay.
That's right.
(Breathing)
After laying the eggs,
- he's exhausted. - He's a sea turtle.
(Daeundea is the perfect place for exercising.)
Muscle Beach.
That's right.
(After a strenuous exercise, he comes back to his senses.)
(Shaking off)
Please don't move.
(Falling)
- How dirty. - Daeundea.
- I support him. - Me too. I'm cheering him on.
You only live once, so you should do what you want.
He really is a dream chaser.
Did you call him a clout chaser?
- A dream chaser. - I heard it as "A clout chaser."
No. A dream chaser.
It's a Finnish sauna.
It's really nice.
I really enjoy it. I use it often.
- I'm really jealous of it. - It's great when you spray water.
(Evaporating)
I'm jealous of that.
(Groaning)
It feels nice.
(My physical exhaustion is dissipating.)
The puffiness will be gone after you enjoy the sauna.
That isn't sticky sweat.
Isn't it an indie movie?
What kind of an indie movie looks like that?
(It was as if he had reincarnated into a turtle,)
(The fetal movement felt real.)
(He sweats as he spaces out between dream and reality.)
(He comes back to reality with sticky sand on his body.)
(There's sand on the floor all over the house.)
He keeps spreading sand.
He'll step on that sand.
- He'll bring sand to MBC as well. - Hold on a second.
- Is there sand under his seat? - No.
(Falling)
(I like nature.)
(He leaves behind the happy Daeundea.)
(I'm hungry from exercising.)
It's okay.
Nana, go inside.
- I washed up. - Go inside.
I felt so refreshed.
Let's see.
(Let's see.)
It was time to eat.
I keep thinking that it's sand.
(He pours starch into a bowl.)
Chicken?
Fried chicken?
I decided to invigorate my tired body.
The most common ingredient for invigorating foods is chicken.
I decided to make a special dish, chicken jeon.
- Chicken jeon. - I'll make jeon...
- with chicken. - Is there such a dish?
Then there's a freshwater fish dish called dori bangbang.
- That's right. - It's a tasty dish.
I'll make chicken wing bangbang, a dish that'll be like a snack.
(Chicken wing bangbang)
It's like dori bangbang.
- You make it with chicken wings. - Yes.
- That's drumstick meat, right? - That's drumstick meat.
It's a tasty dish.
I had chicken jeon for the first time in Busan.
It was so tasty.
It's a dish of Gyeongsang Province.
Let's use some.
(Let's add some chili peppers.)
(As he makes chicken jeon for the first time,)
- Gosh. - I'm making it in my style.
(he adds spiciness as he wants.)
One, two, three.
It looks tasty.
He looks cool.
For the first time, people are showing good reactions.
- When it comes to cooking... - His cooking always gets...
compliments.
To a woman who has the compatible lifestyle,
you'll be the ideal type.
- What? If you say that... - What?
- Joy! - I'm serious.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
To a woman who has the compatible lifestyle.
- She wasn't talking about herself. - She wasn't talking about herself.
(He just laughs.)
- He could be someone's ideal type. - He could be, right?
It's someone else's life.
- There'll be a woman like that. - I'm sure of it.
Now...
(He grabs a package.)
He's making something else.
(He begins to cook noodles for the third dish.)
Noodles?
He cooks with ease.
(He makes three dishes at the same time.)
This is amazing.
(As soon as he flips the chicken jeon...)
- Dae Ho is a great cook. - Right.
It's like it's fried.
The dori bangbang is done like that too.
I'll get some gochujang.
(He quickly makes the sauce by measuring it with his eyes.)
(Applying the sauce right away)
You're using the exact same method.
I used the same sauce as well.
The gochujang sauce.
- It looks good. - That's how it should be done.
- You need a lot of sesame seeds. - It looks insane.
(He swiftly moves onto the next dish.)
Is that naengmyeon?
Yes. Since it's summer.
Is all of that food for one meal?
I binge eat.
He binge eats each day.
You still eat one meal a day, right?
- Yes. - You have one meal a day.
That looks delicious!
(He gets something from on top of the fridge.)
Okay.
What is that?
You have to place it on a griddle.
It's to keep it warm.
You know what that is, right?
- To avoid making it get cold. - I know that.
(He uses even the griddle as it's his first meal.)
- Gosh. - It's great to eat it that way.
I'll get a drink too.
(He even prepares himself a drink.)
I'll go up now.
(He wanders around with the trash bag.)
Time to set things up.
(He puts in a blanket, drink, and glass.)
He's using a trash bag.
What is the trash, and what is not the trash?
This will melt on the way.
(He takes the naengmyeon and chicken wing bangbang.)
Time to set things up.
(He moves over to House 2 with both hands full.)
(He takes one thing after another from the trash bag.)
(He spreads out a towel at Daeundea.)
(He's already full of excitement.)
(He sets the dishes one by one as well.)
(This is great.)
(Like a picnic enjoyed at the beach)
Right. That's the heart he has.
(He puts together a beach picnic at home.)
- The drinks are placed in the sand. - I love that vibe.
You can feel a similar vibe like that.
(Cold naengmyeon that will send away the heat)
- It turned out really nicely. - Gosh!
(Chicken jeon embracing the cheese)
That looks great.
That's amazing.
I'm hungry.
Someone should be invited for a party.
I have no one to call.
(That's not good.)
- That's heartbreaking. - There will be someone, right?
A person who shares similar tastes with me.
(He enjoys the beach picnic just on his own.)
(Impressed)
(Excited)
(He adds the smoky flavor to the chicken jeon.)
The smoky flavor.
(His meal became even more perfect with the torch.)
That's amazing.
(Buzzing)
(A fly comes over after Daeundea opens.)
(He scowls without even knowing that his friend has come.)
Look at that face.
Would anyone still find him to be their ideal type?
Would there be anyone, Joy?
- Where? - A woman who would find him cute?
I believe there will be someone.
- Hopefully. - Even with that face?
(He fills the shaker with vodka.)
(Picking out)
(He pours in the grapefruit juice as well.)
(Grapefruit juice?)
There's a cocktail called the daiquiri in Cuba.
It's a basic cocktail.
- It's a classic. - I went to Cuba...
and I really enjoyed it.
I'm making that right now as it suits the beach vibes.
(He closes the lid so that it doesn't spill.)
(Hitting)
(Shake it!)
(He shakes it with his whole body.)
(He even uses his face muscles.)
Okay.
(Smacking)
(Pulling)
There we go.
This is the daiquiri.
(The orange daiquiri gets poured into the glass.)
(Exclaiming)
- Let's give it a try. - That does look good.
It's good. It tasted good after giving it a shake.
(He picks up the well-mixed cocktail first.)
(Here's to Daeundea.)
(He gulps down as much as he has worked hard.)
Gosh, this is good! Why is this so good?
Having sand in the house is quite luxurious.
That isn't something that is done commonly.
- It's greatly satisfying. - Right.
I mocked it at first, but I think it's quite nice now.
I think it'll be nice to have that at home.
I went there even today.
I see it every day.
- I'm still satisfied with it. - I think it'll be nice.
Won't Nana poop in it?
I can't bring Nana there as he might think of it as a sandbox.
Nana will definitely use it as a sandbox.
Cats usually relieve themselves in sand.
That would be a public restroom for a cat.
Definitely.
Stray cats would use it as well.
- Are you serious? - Or...
Even people might use it!
(The public restroom for people and animals, Daeundea)
I'll keep it just like that. Come and visit.
I should visit before the cats use it.
I'll try this too.
The chicken jeon. Gosh, that must be good.
Gosh, this is insane.
(Groaning)
(Drooling)
It was chewy as it was made with starch.
- The cheese was savory too. - That looks good.
- That looks good. - Gosh.
It had a firm texture as it was made with chicken legs.
- Right. - I'm hungry.
(Groaning)
(It's hot.)
- It's good. - Gosh, that must be good.
(He eats it until the end even though it burns his mouth.)
(He slurps the cold naengmyeon into his hot mouth.)
(The fire has been put out.)
(He wraps the naengmyeon with the chicken jeon.)
That's a great combination.
(Taking in a big slurp)
They went so well together.
(Satisfied)
Was that your first meal...
- after washing the car? - It was my first meal.
- That was why it was so good. - Right.
Along with a sweet cocktail.
(It tastes even better after working hard.)
That would be great.
(Reaching)
The chicken wing bangbang.
It's spicy.
Gosh, that looks good.
(He puts in the whole piece into his mouth...)
(and pulls out the bone.)
(Impressed)
This is insane. It's so good.
It felt a bit like Gcova Chicken.
- With the gochujang sauce. - That makes sense.
It's like Gcova Chicken.
This is so good.
(It's perfect to his taste.)
- Gosh, he's really enjoying it. - He's deboning the wings.
(The endless deboning show carries on.)
(Sucking his fingers)
Gosh, this is happiness.
- This feels like Cebu. - Cebu?
There's no naengmyeon in Cebu.
Right. It's better than Cebu.
(A picnic in Daeundea that competes against Cebu)
(I'm eating a lot better today for some reason.)
(It's unbelievable.)
(Daeundea, a place that makes you forget about Cebu)
To be honest,
I've never been able to enjoy the summer properly this year.
I've never been able to go to the beach this year.
I expected this summer to pass by like this,
but I was able to enjoy a late summer vacation...
and it was truly satisfying.
(Rummaging)
Gosh, there's the scorched rice.
Gosh, it's the scorched rice with cheese.
(Crunchy)
(Barking)
- Hold on. - He doesn't have a dog.
Why is a dog barking while he's eating the cheese?
Oh, that dog has come to pee.
Really?
- It wants the door to be opened. - It needs to use the restroom.
(Should I open the door for it?)
(Look, This is the Life in a Detached House)
(I Live Alone)
Let's go, Dudu.
(A Great Start)
Dudu!
Gosh, it's Dudu!
- He's so cute! - He's so cute!
- That little rascal. - He's so cute.
No. Come this way. The road is too dangerous.
Come this way. There you go.
He's so cute.
- His mouth is so cute. - He's cute, isn't he?
He needs to shave.
- Is that a pimple on your cheek? - Watch your paws, Dudu.
Yes. I covered it up as something came up.
Don't you know that's a trend?
- That? - The zoomers...
cover up their pimples with star-shaped patches.
A lot of patches are applied these days.
(Zoomers use fancy spot patches.)
Did you get some too?
Of course, I did.
Are you serious?
- I'm a zoomer! - Gosh.
You're at an age when you don't get pimples!
- Put them on your age spots. - Age spots?
They are perfect for age spots.
- I can use a big star. - You must go with the big star.
Watch your paws, Dudu.
Where are they going?
Let's go, Dudu!
- Hey! - Dudu!
- Where is this place? - Dudu is here!
Is it an art school?
- It looks like an art school. - It looks like a furniture store.
Isn't it an office?
These are the designers who made...
the one-and-only Lee Jung Sofa in my house.
The female designer is Yu Min.
The male designer is Hwa Chan.
(While living my life, I thought that I only loved dancing.)
(I loved furniture too.)
- Right. - Right.
You learn about this while living your life.
- Aren't I right? - You're right.
(Furniture lover)
(Her favorite is the sofa that she designed herself.)
If you look at it from above...
(A sofa shaped like her initials, "LJ")
(An arrangement of Lee Jung's preferences)
That way it can...
- suit your own lifestyle. - Right.
I've only bought things that were readymade.
(The place where that inspiration comes to life)
That's nice.
(Various artworks can be found within the place.)
They are really famous designers in Korea.
I want to get something made from them too.
You should meet them.
Gosh.
(A harmony of stylish items)
They look pretty.
(There are artworks collected from all over the world too.)
(A place full of ideas)
They have so much style.
Isn't this so different from what we watched earlier?
(Isn't this so different from what we watched earlier?)
- Right. - Why do I want to place some sand?
- No! - No!
They aren't one of us.
- They aren't one of us. - It looks too normal.
You can't do that as they aren't one of us.
It's the Lee Jung Sofa.
The sample.
This is the sample version of the Lee Jung Sofa.
Did you do well to take the wedding photos?
- How did you get them taken? - Well,
I tried putting on all sorts of dresses.
- Should I show you them? - Let's see them.
- Come here, Dudu. - They're a bit funny.
We took some like this.
They're just like all other wedding photos.
Like this.
We're finally seeing proper wedding photos.
Gosh.
We only saw photos of the broom-to-be.
They look amazing.
You two did a photoshoot.
That's not true. It was awkward but fun.
- You two did well. - Right.
Are you using it well?
- The sofa. - Of course.
We mentioned this before.
We wondered what would come next after the Lee Jung Sofa.
- Right. - With that in mind,
- we thought of a Dudu Bed. - Right.
A bed for the dog?
- Right. - Dudu is a family member.
Of course. This really is...
(Listening)
- Dudu is asking for one right now. - Look at him.
- Do you want it made right now? - He's so cute.
Behind the Lee Jung Sofa in the living room,
there's a white cushion.
Well, of course,
getting a readymade product online could be great,
but I wanted to make one for Dudu.
We came up with the idea of making the Dudu Bed.
- There were a lot of dog beds. - Right.
There are a lot of them these days.
Dudu should also try it out.
Look at him wag his tail.
- He knows it's about him. - It's like he knows it's about him.
- Right. - I think he's really smart.
While we're at it,
should we figure out the size?
- It might have to be this size. - Right.
- Dudu is quite big. - Dudu.
- Come here. - Come here.
- Good boy. - Good boy.
- This size seems okay. - This seems right.
- It should be this big. - It should be this big.
This is 90cm by 60cm.
It could be like this with this size.
- He could lie down like this... - He has long legs.
- but also like this. - Right.
Then what's left is the color.
- It should be based on Dudu's fur. - Right.
- To match his personal color. - We have...
many different pieces of fabric here.
- There's a lot of fabric. - We have a lot.
Come up, Dudu.
We can match them with Dudu.
Let's find your personal color, Dudu.
Dudu should choose the fabric.
Right. Dudu will choose himself.
This is what I've heard.
I heard that dogs could only see blue and yellow.
- Right. - Really?
- They can only see those colors. - Right.
That was why...
I thought of yellow.
- Yellow would look nice. - That would look nice.
- That would make it tone on tone. - Right.
- Dudu's fur is yellow too. - Dudu.
- Excuse me, sir. - Excuse me, sir.
We will look for your personal color.
- That's so cute! - Gosh!
- My gosh. - That's so cute!
- Gosh! - That's so cute!
(Moomoo also looked for his personal color.)
But Dudu is a dog.
- Why is my footage shown? - This scene is played here?
- Who is that behind me? - Who is that behind?
- Who is that back there? - Gosh.
That was when I was an artist.
- He looks like a designer. - Right. He does.
- A very sensitive designer. - Right. A very sensitive one.
I was sensitive back then.
(Moomoo's personal color session was almost a failure.)
- That's so cute! - Gosh!
The area around his mouth looks a lot like mine.
- He's so cute! - He's so cute!
- How adorable. - He's so cute!
- My gosh. - No.
Come here, Dudu.
- This one looks nice too. - This one looks nice too.
- This one looks nice, doesn't it? - Right.
- Olive looks nice too. - But...
- does Dudu have a cool tone? - He's so cute.
I can't help it.
Does Dudu have a cool tone?
This brightens up his face, but this one doesn't.
(Unlike Moomoo, who made it difficult with any color...)
- He seems to have a cool tone. - Right. Dudu has a cool tone.
- Dudu has a cool tone. - Right.
- He has a cool tone, doesn't he? - Right.
- Like this. - Right?
Gosh, his face looks so bright. Check this out.
- Why does blue look so good on him? - That looks nice.
(Bright)
- He's so cute! - Those are his colors.
- From a yellow tone, - Right.
we should test out different colors.
It can be made into a patchwork. He wanted to go with that.
(Patchwork: Sewing together pieces of fabric into one piece)
- That looks nice! - That looks nice.
- Right. - Right.
- Like this? - Right.
- They are full of ideas. - Like this?
- Right. - Just like that.
- I think it'll look nice. - It looks nice.
- It looks nice. - Right.
Shall we take a look?
- This is the basic setting. - Right.
- It can be done right away. - Right.
There was a 3D rendering image of the Lee Jung Sofa.
We added the colors to that.
(Impressed)
- Even with that there... - Right.
- That could work. - It's fascinating...
- how that is realized. - Right?
- Instead of that. - Instead of it being orange,
these colors would be better.
I don't want the texture to be too hard.
- It could be attached like this. - That isn't easy to do.
- It makes your head hurt. - Right.
- There are many things to choose. - Right.
There are so many things that need to be considered.
We can see it together when the 3D rendering image comes out.
If you two have the time,
we could visit the factory together.
That would be great.
Thank you, Yu Min.
- Bye. - I'll get going now.
- Go back safely. - Bye.
- Give me a call. - Bye.
- Thank you! - No worries.
(Walking out)
He's so cute.
Let's ride this together, Dudu.
Here.
- Hello. - Gosh, he's so obedient.
- What is this? - Right.
- What? - Whose car is this?
(Pet)
It must be a taxi for people with dogs.
Right. It's a pet taxi.
There's a taxi that can be used with your dog.
(She dozes off as soon as she gets on.)
- He's sleeping with his owner. - He's sleeping well.
(They head back home while taking a nap.)
We're almost there, Dudu.
- Thank you. Goodbye. - Thank you. Goodbye.
Thank you.
Gosh.
We're back home.
We're back home, Dudu.
Hold on, Dudu. Stay here.
Wait, Dudu. Wait right there.
I'll go and wash my hands. Wait right there.
(Come back soon.)
Will he wait right there if he's told to?
Yes. He waits right there for me.
Were you waiting for me?
Come here. Let's wipe you up.
Let's take it off. There you go.
(He stays still even while getting undressed and being wiped.)
Why is he so obedient?
- Gosh, he's so obedient. - Your paw.
He stays still even when I wipe his paws.
Dogs hate it the most when dogs get their paws wiped.
There has to be a tension of being afraid to lose your thumb.
If it was Comme Des... Gosh.
I would've gotten hurt...
during the personal color test.
- Dudu... - I haven't heard him bark.
- He hasn't barked at all. - barely even barks.
(The two of them look happy together even when Dudu's paws get wiped.)
There's no way he likes doing that.
He's being patient...
- based on his personality. - Right.
Dudu.
- Well done, Dudu. - He's such a good dog.
Where's your spot?
Go to your spot.
(He heads straight to his cushion.)
- He has his own spot. - Right.
That was why I really wanted to make him a bed.
Right. It would be great to make him a spot that matches the sofa.
(Dudu's owner finally takes a breather.)
What is that?
- What is that? - Is she taking a driving test?
(License qualification)
I'm taking a driving test.
- On that day? - Yes. On that day.
- The driving test? - For the written test,
(Showing)
I've already passed.
I heard that the written test was hard these days.
I worked hard to study...
and passed with quite a high score.
Nice one.
I wanted to get the Class One license.
I heard it was hard to get the Class One license.
Class One Manual?
- Automatic. - I see.
(Class 2, Class 1)
(Unlike Class 2, where the yellow cars are driven,)
(a 1-ton truck is driven for Class 1.)
Is Class 1 a lot more difficult than Class 2?
- I heard it was really difficult. - Don't even talk about it.
- I drove the big car in Turkiye. - Right.
- There are times when it is needed. - Right.
Do all of you have a driver's license?
I have a Class Two license.
- Same here. - Same here.
Isn't Hyun Moo the only one here with a Class One license?
- Class One Ordinary. - Right.
Many around our age got the Class One Ordinary license.
- Really? - Back then, anything else...
- wasn't considered a real license. - Right.
It's all about changing gears.
- Right. - Class Two was looked down on.
- I see. - "Isn't that for toy cars?"
- This was what was said. - Right.
- A license for bumper cars. - Bumper cars?
It reeks of boomers here.
- It reeks of boomers? - Yes.
Driving must be done like a boomer though.
Of course.
The biggest reason for wanting to get a license...
was because I was Dudu's owner.
- "What if Dudu gets sick?" - That's a big reason.
If I have to take my dog to the hospital urgently,
I can't take a taxi with him in my arms.
I can only take the pet taxi.
That was why I thought I had to have a driver's license.
Listen up, Dudu.
I'll go and take my driving test.
(One last hug before leaving)
I'll give you a hug.
- Look at him leaning on her. - I'll go and do my best.
I'll make sure to do well.
You're trying to keep yourself calm, right?
Yes. I felt so nervous.
So people get nervous for automatic licenses too.
(Laughing)
Bye, Dudu!
I'll go and drive a truck.
She must feel so nervous!
(I'll come back after passing my test.)
(The taxi she called for arrives.)
- Hello. - Welcome.
Thank you, sir.
So there are tests during the day as well.
Right. Tests can be taken at different times these days.
I went early in the morning.
(Her heart is beating quickly.)
I'm feeling so nervous.
I took an ox bezoar pill.
I'm feeling nervous too.
I was getting crazy nervous from there.
I think it's better to get a license in summer.
Why?
Strangely, you get more nervous in winter.
- Because it's too cold. - Your hands freeze.
- That's because it's cold. - That's only natural!
- You're saying the obvious. - No, it's...
- I get what you mean. - You get it, right?
- I get what he means. - I mean...
You don't start right away for the practical test.
- You have to wait for your turn. - It gets cold.
Because it was cold and I was nervous,
I kept shaking, when I'm not the type to.
- That's right! It... - I remember shaking like this.
- It affects you. - That's right.
- I know. - Did you all pass...
the practical test at once?
- I... - I passed at once.
I passed at once too.
I failed, though.
I failed too.
When you fail the practical test, they announce it so loudly...
- that it's humiliating. - I know.
They couldn't have gone, "Joy of Red Velvet, you failed."
- "Joy of Red Velvet?" - But...
Red flavor
- Joy. - Red flavor
You failed
- Everyone there... - Red flavor, you failed
But...
(Exploding with red flavor that makes your face go red)
(After driving for a while, she almost reached her destination.)
When you turn left or right...
(Suddenly getting nervous)
(Worried)
- It makes you really nervous. - I was really nervous.
I feel like throwing up, watching this.
You're here.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Have a good day.
(Today's destination she finally reached)
(She gets out filled with worries.)
(Plodding)
(She walks somewhere.)
What is this?
- Hello. - Hello.
What is that?
- Oh, my. - What is this?
It's a driving simulator training center that uses a screen.
(A center where you can practice using a simulator indoors)
- What a world we live in. - Oh, my.
That's fascinating.
The frame, gear shift, wheel, and everything else...
are exactly the same.
(People who dream of becoming the best drivers)
I thought I'd get less nervous...
when I drive a real car if I practiced with the simulator.
There was only so much you could learn from YouTube.
There was only so much I could ask too.
I went there yesterday too, and I practiced for four hours.
- Four hours? - Yes.
I drove to Busan using the simulator.
But you can get the license right away these days...
because there are so many well-made videos online.
- That's true. - Really?
I heard there were many people who studied on their own.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
(She practices before taking the test.)
(Taking a seat)
After adjusting the seat...
(She adjusts the seat first.)
It's exactly the same as the test.
- Gosh, that's realistic. - How nerve-racking!
The time limit is 9 minutes and 50 seconds.
- That's right. - Oh, right.
- There's a time limit. - There's a time limit.
- I know. - Step on the brake.
When the needle goes up, it means the car's started.
We will begin now.
The voice sounds exactly the same.
Release the handbrake.
So it's really lifelike.
(Nervous)
Be careful not to go over 20km.
Then a green light will come on.
That's when you need to turn off the turn signal.
(Turning it off with one hand)
(Focused)
- Lower the speed by ten percent. - Yes, you need to go slowly.
- You should barely step on the gas. - From here...
Stop here for three seconds.
Check if it's been three seconds.
- Then you can go. - It's really nerve-racking...
not to step on the line.
(A left turn right in front)
You can even stop when you turn.
- She's pretty good. - Stop if it feels risky.
- Stop if it feels risky. - Oh, no!
(Disqualified)
What?
- You bumped into the wall? - Yes.
- How did you bump into it? - I mean...
I find turning left and right really hard.
I can't figure it out. How much I need to turn...
- How much you need to turn? - That's right.
How much I need to turn...
- at which point. - You can't call that turning left.
I really can't tell.
That's really important, though.
You're developing a sense for it.
That's the most difficult part.
(Disqualified)
You get disqualified right away if you bump into it?
Yes, you get disqualified right away.
It's so scary.
Fortunately, it'll get easier when you are there.
- This could be even more difficult. - That could be the case.
- That's why it's hard. - It's different from a real car.
(Turning)
You need to turn more.
- Disqualified. - Oh, you can tell right away...
- that I need to turn more. - Yes, you need to turn more.
You need to be careful of that.
(It's finally time for the T-shaped parking section.)
(Nervous)
(Turning right as she enters the parking space)
(Almost stepping on the line)
(Checking the side-view mirrors with sharp eyes)
(Shifting the gear to reverse)
(Carefully reversing while watching the line)
You can't step on the line.
(Lining up the tires with the parking line)
(Then she reverses straight.)
You're good. It's hard to park.
There were preset parking techniques I didn't know of.
Parallel parking is the difficult one.
- But it's not included, right? - It's not.
- There's no parallel parking? - There's no parallel parking?
Oh, my. You scared me.
- Seriously... - No parallel parking means...
- I can't approve of it. - I mean...
Do you think you'll do parallel parking more...
or T-shaped parking more when you're on the road?
- But these days, - You'll do parallel parking more.
parallel parking isn't included.
- There's only T-shaped parking. - Everyone, return your licenses.
- I had to do parallel parking. - I did too.
- I did too. - Then I approve of it.
Why must we get your approval?
- You're right. - Exactly.
- What is this? - I almost failed...
because of parallel parking.
It was really hard.
(Riding the momentum)
(Fumbling)
(Putting on glasses)
Focus.
(Getting back to the practice after putting on glasses to focus)
- It's good. - Yes, it's good.
I can do it.
Good luck.
(She presses her lips to focus.)
(She faces the left-turn section.)
- Turn. - Turn more.
(Halting)
- You need to go really slowly. - That's right.
She made it.
It looks like she's used to it now.
Parking is the most difficult,
but it looks like she'll pass at this rate.
Excuse me, can I try this one more time?
Well done.
That's why you keep practicing.
It's because she's anxious. Just in case...
- That's right. - Practice is the only way.
Don't worry too much, and don't be too nervous.
The simulator is more difficult than the real one.
(After a long practice...)
Don't be nervous.
You can do well if you don't get nervous.
But I'm really nervous.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Great job.
My biggest motto is,
"Let's try it anyway."
There's nothing more important than experience.
So let's give it a try.
Let's try hard.
(Weeping)
What do I do?
(She heads to the test site across the road, filled with worries.)
(Sighing)
(Thinking)
(Standing demurely)
(The light changed.)
(Skipping)
She's stepping on them on purpose...
- because of the test. - You're right.
- To not jinx the test... - You're right.
Oh, a jinx?
She doesn't want to step on the line.
- You can't step on the line. - No, you can't.
(She passes the main gate without stepping on the line.)
(Let's see.)
(Here we go.)
(Now she's only stepping on the red bricks.)
- It's because of a jinx. - That's important.
- Seriously. - But you stepped on the blue line.
No, I didn't!
She stepped on the line on the crosswalk too.
- That's not true! - I saw it too.
- You saw it too, right? - Yes.
Take that back.
Is it here?
Hello.
What can I help you with?
I'm here for the practical test.
Please give me your ID.
Here you go.
Please go to the building on the right outside.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
(Entering the test site with the application form in her arms)
Is that it? Is that the truck I'm going to be driving?
(The truck for the test caught Jung's eyes.)
You're getting on the truck...
- for the first time? - That's right.
(Surprised)
I think it's this course.
Yes, that's the one.
Gosh, it was overwhelming.
(The tests are actually being held.)
You need to get a good car too.
- If you get a weird one... - That's right.
(It's more nerve-racking to see it in person.)
(Sniffling)
Hello.
(To the quiet waiting room for the practical test)
- You always wait there... - That's right.
and watch others taking the test.
(Hitting)
Jung is really brave, though.
You need to try getting in the car.
Right? To take the test without getting in the car before...
But I asked around,
- and they all said... Yes. - They did what you did?
They gave it a try...
- without trying a real car. - Yes, that's possible.
Their generation watches videos a lot.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
(The video-generation Jung is still nervous.)
(Sighing)
The 4pm test will begin now.
Ms. Lee Ji Young.
(They announce the start of the test.)
- The narration makes you nervous. - That's right.
- I wish she could be sweeter. - She sounds really mean.
(The other test takers prepare for their tests first.)
(There are 4 sections.)
(A ramp, turn,)
(intersection)
The changed test isn't easy.
(You can only pass if you get over 80.)
(The 1st test taker takes off 1st.)
(Here they go!)
Even though they were strangers, I couldn't help but root for them.
- That's right. - They were complete strangers.
(Turning)
(She practices in the air out of desperation.)
Car number 29. It stepped on the parking line number 4.
- You can't step on the line. - When you see that,
you'll be mentally out of it.
(The test is being broadcast in real time.)
Car number 23 is disqualified.
If the test takers before you get disqualified,
it drives you crazy.
(Disqualified as soon as it started)
It got disqualified as soon as it started?
You get disqualified if you start without releasing the handbrake.
They started without releasing the handbrake?
Yes, but there are quite a lot of people who make such mistakes.
- I did. - That's right.
Well, I didn't release...
The handbrake?
Yes, so I got disqualified right away.
Actually, the pass rate of the practical test...
- is only about 30 percent. - Really?
Because you're nervous, you forget what you already know.
Yes, you forget what you're always aware of.
- That's right. - That's right.
Car number 18. It stepped on the parking line number 2.
Car number 13 is disqualified.
It sounds like the voice from "Squid Game."
- It does sound like "Squid Game." - Exactly.
It's disqualified.
(The test takers get disqualified in a row.)
Car number 18. It's disqualified on the ramp.
(Switching the driver as they're disqualified)
- It's really embarrassing then. - I know.
The test taker was dragged out like GTA.
Car number 29. Congratulations.
- You passed. - That was the first person to pass.
Good for them.
Car number 30. Congratulations.
(Envious)
(The rest of them are being called one by one.)
(The waiting room starts to get empty.)
When will my turn come?
(Jung is the only one left in the waiting room.)
Am I the last one?
(Am I the last to go?)
(Shaking)
Gosh, what's with the cloud?
Oh, no. A crow.
(Anxious)
My stomach hurts because I'm nervous.
That's right.
That's why you need to use the restroom before.
- You must go. - For real.
Ms. Lee Jung.
(It's finally my turn.)
She's doing it now.
(After identity verification...)
Get in car number three.
Car number three.
(I'm nervous.)
- Ms. Lee Jung. - Yes.
Please come this way.
That's when your hands start to get cold.
Yes, and they shake too.
(She heads to the truck for the test with clenched fists.)
Thank you.
Yes.
(Let's not forget the seatbelt.)
You can do it.
- Follow the instructions relaxedly. - Okay.
It's here, and this is here.
(Quickly scanning the inside)
- We'll begin. - All right.
Car number three. Ms. Lee Jung is ready.
- Good luck. - "Good luck."
Stay calm.
(Sighing)
(Shaking)
- Don't shake your legs. - It was real.
- Don't shake your legs! - Why are you shaking so much?
- That was... I was seriously... - Hold on.
- I... - She lost all her good luck.
I was really nervous that I...
- I get it, but... - That'd drive your fortune out.
You lost all your good luck.
But what was I supposed to do? I was so nervous.
(Barely holding on to her trembling heart)
(Into the world of driving)
The test will begin for car number three.
I was really nervous.
(Sighing)
- This is nothing. - We will begin the test.
- It's nothing. - Your points might get deducted...
if you use any parts different from the instruction,
so please keep that in mind.
Why can't I stay still?
We will begin the test now.
Start the engine within five seconds.
(The test begins with operating the drive controls.)
(Clicking)
We will begin the test now.
Turn on the left turn signal within five seconds.
It's really nerve-racking that there are only five seconds.
Turn off the turn signal within five seconds.
Some people turn on the wipers by mistake.
- Oh, not the turn signals? - Oh, right. The wipers.
Shift the gear lever to neutral, then switch it back...
- to the parking position... - There were such tests.
- within ten seconds. - I totally forgot.
Shift to N and then to P.
(Jung calmly does what she's learned.)
(Exhaling)
Watching that makes me nervous again.
Now, we will test your basic driving ability.
We will begin now.
- Break a leg. - Good luck.
Release the brake and start.
She released the handbrake.
(Exhaling)
That's it.
Why am I breathing so hard?
You're really calm comparatively.
(She sets off without deducting any points.)
That was good.
This is nothing.
Jung, it's okay even if you fail.
Just try hard and do your best.
Focus, all right?
I did that too. I talked to myself.
You tend to speak to yourself a lot.
I've never seen you getting this nervous.
It's been so long since I got that nervous too.
(She's arrived at the ramp, the second section.)
- Stop. - This part is important.
- Oh, don't cross the line. - The line.
- Do it calmly. Step on the brake. - The line. Good job.
So far, she's doing well.
You're doing well.
(Wait for 3 seconds.)
(She goes after keeping the time.)
That's good. You're doing well.
Drive slowly.
There you go. Drive slowly.
There you go. Go slowly.
Focus.
There you go. Be careful here...
because you're turning left here.
- This part. - Gosh, this part.
- All right. Turn the wheel. - Go slowly.
(The corner turning section wasn't easy during practice also.)
You'll get disqualified for sure if you bump into that.
Your points don't get deducted. You get disqualified right away.
(This is too hard.)
From here...
Stay calm.
(Even I'm more nervous.)
(Sweating profusely)
- Good. - Yes. I think it's good.
There you go. You did well.
- You're doing well. - You did well.
Go slowly.
Turn left here.
Turn now.
Gosh, this is so stressful.
(Turning the wheel breathlessly)
There you go! You're doing well.
(Please...)
There you go. That's good.
(She passes the next left-turn section as well!)
- You're doing well. - Shall I check? So far, so good.
It was smoother than I thought.
I saw how my points didn't get deducted at all,
so I thought I was a genius.
(Amazed)
(Maybe I'm a genius who's good at real games.)
It was a lot easier, right?
- It was rather easier... - That's right.
than the stimulator.
It's red light, so step on the brake.
- Oh, I can go now. - You're doing well.
Go a bit further from here.
Why am I shaking so much?
You're dancing with your foot.
(Holding on to her trembling body and driving slowly)
(Squirming)
It's parking.
You're good at parking.
I'm confident in parking.
Where should I park?
- Go to number one. - Oh, thank you.
What was I to do from here? All right. Let's see.
Position the car in line with your shoulder. That's it.
- Oh, no. Your shoulder. - Oh, dear.
- It's okay. - Oh, no.
Go slowly. There you go.
You're stepping on the brake too much.
Because I stepped on it too hard,
my butt hurt so much.
When your butt doesn't hurt from dancing so much?
Seriously, my butt hurt a lot.
- You stepped on it too hard. - Yes.
If someone were in the passenger seat, they'd have thrown up.
That's for sure.
(Gagging)
All right. Turn it all the way.
(Rushed)
Let's go.
There you go. You're doing well.
- You did well. - She entered the section.
Turn it only half way, and where do I go?
You need to check that.
- There you go. Go slowly. - That's it.
You're doing well.
Gosh, is this right?
I have no idea.
(Exhaling)
(Even her cheek is shaking.)
- She's so nervous. - Oh, no.
- Slow down! - It's like...
It's like she's defusing a time bomb.
- It's because we know how it feels. - That's right.
- You get it, right? - I hate it.
You're not talking to someone in the back, are you?
"Is this right?"
Like I'm talking to a friend. "Is this right?"
(Getting ready to park while talking to herself)
Reverse. Now, back up slowly.
(Turning)
She's doing well.
- Look at her face. - Stay calm.
She did well.
(She pushes the tail in without hesitating.)
(Rocking)
You're doing well.
(Look how charismatic she is.)
Hey, slow down.
"Is this right?"
She steps on the brake really aggressively.
Because she doesn't have a sense for it yet.
Release it all the way.
- Oh, no. There you go. - Release it all the way.
Release it all the way. Back up straight.
- Yes, back up after releasing. - Back up straight.
- All right. You did it. - Go slowly.
- It's approved. - All right.
(She managed to park without deducting points.)
You did well.
Gosh, thank you.
(That's amazing.)
(Watch...)
(the parking skill of a genius.)
Release the handbrake and shift to D.
The shoulder line.
Align the car to the shoulder line.
- Then move out. - That's it. It's here.
- It's here. There you go. - There you go.
"Is your shoulder line here?"
Gosh, that's totally...
(Let's go to the next course!)
Your points are deducted for stepping on the line.
No!
Gosh, what is this?
(Shocked)
(No, please...)
You should watch as you go.
All right. It's okay.
It's okay. Just give up. It's all right.
It doesn't matter.
Right. You didn't have any points deducted.
- I just need to keep going. - Just go.
- Your points are deducted. - What's wrong?
Your points are deducted for stepping on the line.
You can't go back and forth.
- No. Just go. - Just hurry up and go.
If you go back and forth here, your points...
- will keep getting deducted. - Just go!
(Everyone is coaching her desperately.)
(It's frustrating for her even now.)
- You should just hurry and leave. - You should just leave.
Run away.
No.
I can't lose any more points now.
If you make one more mistake, you'll be disqualified?
Hold on, Jung. Calm down.
Let's back up a bit.
- Back up? - Why would you back up?
- No! - Don't back up!
Why would you back up?
No, let's just go.
- Go forward. - Go forward.
That's right.
(Shaking)
What's wrong?
- What's wrong? - Because she's scared,
she stepped on the brake.
What's wrong? What are you doing?
(The car went up onto the curb.)
You're disqualified by authority.
(A bolt out of the blue)
No!
- Bye. - Bye.
- But seriously... - You're disqualified, right?
See you again.
- What was that about? - I mean... I...
You passed all the difficult parts.
I was so dumbfounded too.
But once you get your points deducted in a row...
- That's when you lose your cool. - Right. You'd lose your cool.
You just lost your cool.
I really thought I was in "Squid Game."
You could've gotten 4.56 million dollars.
You died at the end.
- I thought she'd pass. - Me too.
- It's a bummer. - Naturally.
Wouldn't you have passed if you just crossed the finish line?
- I had to pass the intersection... - Right?
and speed up.
Oh, you have to drive fast at the end?
- The speeding section. - Right. There's that too.
- Speeding is easy. - Right.
That was close.
(She was disqualified by authority when she almost made it.)
(I can't believe it ended like this.)
That was close.
(Why do I keep tearing up like this?)
You'd tear up then.
Let me take over.
Thank you.
Please get out.
"Please get out."
- Thank you. - They drag you out so meanly.
- Like GTA. - Sit in the back.
- In the back? - Yes.
Thank you.
(Exiled to the backseat)
(Crying)
(Ending the test, leaving regrets behind)
(I'm an 8t truck with a broken wheel)
(She parked well but went the wrong way.)
(A wheel turning mistake too late to undo)
(Crying)
(I want to go back.)
You get to go on a drive. Sitting at the back looks cool.
You look like a rich lady.
But I failed the test.
- Thank you. - Go to the second floor.
- The second floor? - Yes.
That's the most embarrassing moment.
It's the most embarrassing for real.
- I've never been that embarrassed. - Thank you.
(Hitting)
Oh, dear.
(Stumbling)
I hit it too hard.
(She just laughs, forgetting the pain.)
No...
What did I do wrong?
If I reversed...
I should've turned this way and gone that way.
(Sighing)
She passed all the difficult sections.
- I know. - You're right. She did.
- It's a bummer. - She should've failed...
- in the beginning. - That's right.
(It's not easy to get a driver's license.)
She'll pass next time.
You're right.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
That was really close.
I have to go and get "fail" stamped.
- It's already sad... - Hello.
- That's a bit... - that she failed.
- And she has to get that too? - Oh, right.
You can come back again.
Thank you. Goodbye.
- She got the mark for "fail." - How embarrassing.
It was humiliating.
(Looking for somewhere to hide)
How futile.
(Crying)
When can you retake the test?
After failing,
you need to wait three days to give it a try again.
(She comes outside looking down.)
The weather was especially nice.
(Jung calls someone.)
(Who could it be?)
- Hello. - Dad.
Yes.
I just took the practical test, and I failed.
- You failed? - Yes.
(She whines to her dad as she's disappointed.)
There are two ways.
Getting a license no matter what...
and driving yourself.
Yes.
Or cutting off driving in your life...
and not driving could be another way.
- That's a solution too. - Of course.
You're right.
But even if I don't drive, I must get the Type One license.
It's really firing me up.
- Right. It fires you up. - Yes, it does.
Sure. Go ahead and try. You can get it.
- All right, Dad. - All right.
I felt really grateful for everyone...
who drives for me.
First of all, there's my mom and dad.
And Yoon Seo who sometimes picks me up...
or drives me home.
And the taxi drivers and bus drivers who always drive for me.
I have huge respect for everyone on the road...
- who drives safely. - Yes, you feel love for humankind.
That's right.
- I'll call you again. - All right.
- Okay, rest well. - Okay.
Bye.
(And I Will Give It a Try Again)
(Next story)
(To meet special people,)
(he has arrived somewhere.)
(Yeongcheon National Cemetery)
(His grandfather and grandmother...)
(who are people of national merit)
Here it is.
(Have you been well?)
(Army Sergeant First Class)
(The rain stopped miraculously when he was about to give a bow.)
(The day my grandmother passed...)
(was the same date as my birthday.)
(The past days he disregarded his birthday as he was sad)
(He just calmly...)
(spent his birthdays.)
(To me, family means...)
(the assurance that I'll have something to fall back on,)
(no matter what I lose.)
(Ki Bum, come out for lunch.)
(He visited his house in Daegu after a long time.)
(Surprised)
(You made it yourself? You didn't get it from the supermarket?)
(All of them?)
(I can do this much.)
(Beef tripe in bone soup?)
(The bone soup recipe they missed...)
(that they couldn't eat but just kept to themselves)
- Does it taste the same? - It's good.
(It tastes the same.)
(Always Feeling You)
(Ju Seung visited many wedding halls at the end of last year.)
(Thanks to him, his brother's wedding went well.)
(After the wedding, they gathered at their parents' place.)
(And Ga Eul, his sister-in-law who is from Vietnam)
They're doing something.
(Where did they go to with a new family member?)
(Let me teach you more about Korean culture...)
(at Korean Folk Village.)
(Walking cozily)
(Linking arms with each other)
(Shall I take a photo for you?)
(Jutographer for his sister-in-law)
(How should I pose? I have no idea.)
(Shy)
One, two, three.
(Suddenly changing in front of the camera)
(I'll take photos with all my heart.)
It's so pretty.
(The customer is highly satisfied.)
I'm different as I'm a pro.
(I proved myself, didn't I?)
(Stretching)
(Jutographer does his best.)
(I gave it my all.)
(Welcome, Sister-in-Law)